hey everybody welcome to another english
listening quiz this quiz will test your
listening comprehension skills and help
you learn the real sounds of english
before we start remember to download the
listening time podcast and if you need
my help to improve your listening skills
then click on the link in the
description below this video to become a
listening time member and you'll receive
my listening practice seminars which
will help you understand native speakers
when they speak fast and if you become a
listening time family member you'll get
my advanced podcast episodes which will
help you reach an advanced level of
listening okay are you ready for the
quiz here's the first question which of
these am i saying
the music will start
the correct answer is c in english the
word will is usually reduced to o so the
phrase music will is reduced to musical
it sounds the same as the word musical
alright here's the next question which
of these words am i saying
bot
the correct answer is b
the word b-o-u-g-h-t
is pronounced bot with the mouth wide
open and the tongue low
bot
the word b-u-t is pronounced but with a
relaxed mouth
but and the word b-o-a-t is pronounced
boat with rounded lips
boat
okay next question what's the second
word that i'm saying in this sentence
four or five of them left
the second word in that sentence is or
listen again
four or five of them left
the phrase for or is reduced to four
listen
four or five of them left
all right last question what sentence am
i saying
if only you could stay a bit longer
write your answer in a comment down
below okay before we go remember to
download the listening time podcast and
click on the link in the description
below this video to become a listening
time member and you'll receive my
training which will help you understand
fast english and if you want my advanced
podcast episodes then become a listening
time family member also remember to
subscribe to the channel click on the
bell and follow us on instagram i'll see
you next time
you